gagadaily.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Gaga Daily

**Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Log files**  
Like many other websites, we make use of log files. Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website’s web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user’s IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

**Third party advertising**  
We use third-party advertising powered by Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on GagaDaily.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to GagaDaily.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Analytics**  
We use the Google Analytics web service to monitor statistics of this website. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Privacy contact**  
If you feel that this Website is not following this Privacy Policy, you may [contact us](mailto:contact@gagadaily.com?subject=PRIVACY-CONTACT) at with your concerns.
